<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About the Assembly of Citizens on Assembly of Citizens</title>
    <link>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About the Assembly of Citizens on Assembly of Citizens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The speech by Litong Lin on the 32nd anniversary of Tiananmen Square Protest</title>
      <link>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/archive/2022-06-04-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/archive/2022-06-04-speech/</guid>
      <description>The speech by Litong Lin on the 32nd anniversary of Tiananmen Square Protest Ladies and gentlemen, my name is Litong Lin, the representative of Assembly of Citizens. I am honored to have the opportunity to speak here.
The host had just said that our organization and I are &amp;ldquo;standing up and resisting the autocratic tyranny of CCP.&amp;rdquo; If we compare ourselves to the men and women who gave their lives for a better China or to the braves who were thrown into prison because of their actions of striving for unalienable human rights, we must say we can&amp;rsquo;t afford this reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/info/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/info/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Event Schedule from August to October 2022 August Week 1: Introduction to the Existential Problem: Sexualization and Lacan&amp;rsquo;s Existential Problem
Week 2: China’s New World Order? (Part I)
Discuss Rush Doshi’s The Long Game: China&amp;rsquo;s Grand Strategy to Displace American Order
Week 3: Documentary: A Touch of Sin (by Jia Zhangke)
September: Week 1: China’s New World Order? (Part I) Discuss Rush Doshi’s The Long Game: China&amp;rsquo;s Grand Strategy to Displace American Order</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/info/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://assemblyofcitizens.org/en/info/principles/</guid>
      <description>Our Principles 1. Three main goals As a political activist group, our activity has three main goals:
1.1. To serve: Loneliness, anxiety, and depression are very common among young dissidents. The first thing that tyranny destroys is the relationship among persons. The tyranny is also hostile to the cooperation of people. We will serve the young dissidents by providing a platform of communication, study, and mutual help, which aim to rebuild cordial relationships among people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>